https://www.westone.com/store/index.php/privacy-policy

array(3) {
["width_config"] => string(0) ""
["header-top"] => array(2) {
[0] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(121) "{"type":"static_block","title":"Top Welcome Homepage","identifier":"top-welcome-homepage","block_id":"59","store_id":"1"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(51) "border-dash col-lg-6 col-md-6 col-sm-12 ui-sortable"
}
[1] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(100) "{"type":"static_block","title":"Add This","identifier":"share_social","block_id":"5","store_id":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(39) "border-dash col-lg-6 col-md-6 col-sm-12"
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(78) "{"type":"custom","id":"3","title":"Site Logo","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(52) "border-dash col-lg-3
col-md-3 col-xs-12 ui-sortable"
}
[1] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(103) "{"type":"static_block","title":"June5Banner","identifier":"june5banner","block_id":"85","store_id":"1"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(50) "border-dash col-lg-9 col-md-9 col-sm-9 ui-sortable"
Personal Information
Westone may ask you to register and provide personal information, such as when you purchase products from our online store, register new products, access product information, features or programs, enter a contest or sweepstakes, or sign into a page that requires authorization. Westone may also collect credit card information to bill you for products and services that you purchased. This personal information may include your name, e-mail address, user ID, domain name, URL, mailing address, and telephone number. Westone may also collect demographic information such as your age, gender, zip code/postal code, education level, household income, operating system, preferences, interests, favorites, and whether you are a personal or business user. If you choose not to register and provide this information, you can still use most of Westone’s Web site. Unfortunately, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.
Children's Personal Information
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have such personal information, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information.
System Configuration Information
Westone automatically collects on our server logs certain information about your computer hardware and software when you visit our Web site or use Westone’s online services. This information may include such things as your IP address, cookie information, globally unique identifier, system, operating system, a description of any Westone products connected and how such products are used, browser type, domain names, access times, service provider and referring Web site addresses.
Web Site Usage Information
Westone and its third party service providers track non-personally identifiable information about how you use our website through cookies, globally unique identifiers, Internet tags or web beacons in the aggregate, and track navigational data (log files, server logs, click stream). These allow us to track how you interact with Westone online, and, with your permission, we can tie this information to your personal information to help us tailor communication to you. We also collect information such as the URL of the Web site you previously visited, and when you use our Web site. Westone also keeps track of the pages you visit within our Web site and any transaction details (downloads, orders, requests, or referrals). You can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse or delete cookies altogether, but certain features of our Web site might not work.
Personal Information
With your express permission, Westone collects, integrates, and uses your personal information to help enhance and personalize your use of our Web site, products and services. This will enable the following: (1) you to quickly find services or information on www.westone.com (2) Westone to create Web site content and other services most relevant or customized to you, (3) for you to be alerted about product and Web site upgrades and updates, special offers, promotions, newsletters, latest product announcements, upcoming events, programs and other new products from Westone; and (4) to invite you to participate in product and service surveys or programs. Westone uses this information to communicate with you either via the Internet, e-mail, mail or telephone only after you give your express permission for such communication. (The only exception to this Statement are “service e-mails” that may notify you about system downtimes, product problems or recalls, password reminder e-mails, etc.), We also use anonymous and aggregated data to create statistics and reports for various business purposes. We may aggregate anonymous data and share the anonymous data with our co-marketing partners in order to offer all our customers potentially desirable products and services as well as to improve our content and services. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information (such as e-mail address) that they need to deliver the service. Our service providers are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. From time to time we supplement the information we collect from the site with information from offline or third party sources. We use this information to enhance or overlay the “profile” of customers and business contact information. This supplementary data is therefore tied to corporate contact information and in some cases personally identifiable information. We also may internally compare lists collected from our other sites or within our family of companies to remove duplicate entries.
E-Mail Messaging
Westone will periodically send our registered users e-mail messages about our products and services. When sending you e-mail, we may use an image called a single pixel GIF that allows us to format messages tailored to your computer’s capabilities. We also use this technology to determine, in the aggregate, how many people open our e-mails. When you initiate a response by clicking on a link within an e-mail, you are redirected onto the Internet. We then record your individual response to help us deliver information that is more relevant to your interests.
Disclosure of Information
Westone keeps your personally identifiable information confidential. We do not disclose it to third parties or others that do not have a need to know such information except under certain circumstances. Set forth below are additional circumstances where Westone may share your personal information: A certain number of our employees, independent contractors and service providers may have access to your personally identifiable information necessary for the sole purpose of helping us run our business. These employees and contractors have confidentiality and security obligations. Some affiliates, subsidiaries and third party service providers as we deem appropriate. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to another business entity should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity; or to any organization involved in a merger, transfer, or sale of our assets or business.Before we disclose your personally identifiable data for other reasons, we will first obtain your consent, for example via e-mail, click-through, an online opportunity to opt-out, or otherwise. If you post any information in public areas of our Web site, such as chat rooms and message boards, it will be available to the public and we may reuse and republish such information at our discretion and in accordance with our Terms of Use. To protect and defend the rights or property of Westone, including its Web sites. We may also share your personally identifiable information to respond to law enforcement requests, court orders or other legal processes or if we believe that such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent or respond to illegal activities, fraud, physical threats to you or others, national security threats or as otherwise required by any applicable law or regulation. In the event that we disclose your personally identifiable information as set out above, we will require third party organizations that have access to your personally identifiable information to protect and maintain your personally identifiable information in compliance with the terms and conditions of this Statement.
Prohibited Disclosures
Except as set forth above, Westone will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party, including advertisers, without your explicit consent. In addition, Westone will not share, trade, rent, or otherwise disclose your personal information, Westone’s e-mail list or address list to third parties for their promotional purposes.
Safe Harbor Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Westone or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
Protection of Information Westone is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
Changes to This StatementWestone will occasionally update this Statement. When Westone posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Statement link on the front page of www.westone.com If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Westone will use your personal information, Westone will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. In any case we will not make any changes that are less protective of your personal information collected in the past without your consent. Westone encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Westone is protecting your information.
News Category
Press
Events
Westone Laboratories
Since 1959, Westone has specialized in custom earpieces, earphones, and many other products to protect and enhance hearing, facilitate communication, and support Hearing Health Care professionals.
Our dedication to absolute quality, uncompromising service, and The Golden Rule have made us a world leader in our industry.
Get In Touch
Westone Laboratories2235 Executive CircleColorado Springs, Colorado80906, USA
P.O. Box 15100Colorado Springs, CO 80935
Phone: 1-800-525-5071Music Support: 1-877-290-3988Email: Contact Westone
Location on Google Maps
© 2020 Westone Laboratories. All Rights Reserved.
You have no items in your shopping cart.
